Guide to the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council, Seattle Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America District Council Seattle records, 1918-1972; 1851-001; 8.21 cubic feet (8 boxes)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1919-1972; SERIES III (Box-folder 1/4-4/19)
    - Incoming Correspondence, 1919-1968; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/4-2/59)
      - US Construction Corps Camp F-23, 1933 (Box-folder 2/31)
      - US Commerce Dept. President's Conference on Unemployment, 1923 (Box-folder 2/32)
      - Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 2/33)
      - US Dept. of Interior Bureau of Reclamation, 1934 (Box-folder 2/34)
      - US Dept. of Labor Bureau of Labor-Management Report, 1959 (Box-folder 2/35)
      - US Dept. of Labor Bureau of Labor Standards, 1957 (Box-folder 2/36)
      - US Dept. of Labor Office of the Secretary, 1934 (Box-folder 2/37)
      - US Dept. of Labor US Employment Service, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 2/38)
      - US Dept. of Labor Wage Adjustment Board, 1945 (Box-folder 2/39)
      - US Dept. of Labor Wage Stabilization Board, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/40)
      - US Dept. of Labor Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 2/41)
      - US War Manpower Commission. US Employment Service, 1943 (Box-folder 2/42)
      - US National Recovery Administration, 1934 (Box-folder 2/43)
      - US National Labor Relations Board, 1954-1960 (Box-folder 2/44)
      - US National War Labor Board, 12th Regional War Labor Board, 1944 (Box-folder 2/45)
      - US Works Progress Administration, 1935 (Box-folder 2/46)
      - Wahr, Ceeil, 1961 (Box-folder 2/47)
      - Wallgren, Mon C., 1933-1935 (Box-folder 2/48)
      - Washington Emergency Relief Admin. District No. 2, 1934 (Box-folder 2/49)
      - State of Wash. Dept. of Highways, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 2/50)
      - State of Wash. Dept. of Labor and Industries, 1927 (Box-folder 2/51)
      - State of Wash. Executive Dept., 1932 (Box-folder 2/52)
      - Supreme Court State of Wash., 1937 (Box-folder 2/53)
      - Wash. State Federation of Labor, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 2/54)
      - Washington State Grange, 1943 (Box-folder 2/55)
      - West Coast Lumbermen's Association, 1928-1933 (Box-folder 2/56)
      - Headquarters Western Defense Command and Fourth Army, 1943 (Box-folder 2/57)
      - Zioncheck, Marion A, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 2/58)
      - District Council of Carpenters, Uncatalogued, 1943-1968 (Box-folder 2/59)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1919-1968; Subseries B (Box-folder 2/60-2/77)
      - District Council of Carpenters., 1919-1923 (Box-folder 2/60)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1923-1928 (Box-folder 2/61)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1929 (Box-folder 2/62)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1930 (Box-folder 2/63)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1931 (Box-folder 2/64)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1932 (Box-folder 2/65)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1933 (Box-folder 2/66)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1934 (Box-folder 2/67)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1935 (Box-folder 2/68)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1936 (Box-folder 2/69)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1937 (Box-folder 2/70)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 2/71)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1945-1949 (Box-folder 2/72)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1950-1956 (Box-folder 2/73)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 2/74)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1959 (Box-folder 2/75)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 2/76)
      - District Council of Carpenters, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 2/77)
    - General Correspondence, 1923-1972; Subseries C (Box-folder 2/78-4/15)
      - Adak, Alaska, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 2/78)
      - Alaska Council of Carpenters, 1952-1962 (Box-folder 2/79)
      - Alaska Salmon Industry, 1938-1943 (Box-folder 2/80)
      - Alaska Salmon Industry, 1944 (Box-folder 2/81)
      - Alaska Salmon Industry, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 2/82)
      - Alaska Salmon Industry, 1947-1952 (Box-folder 2/83)
      - Building and Construction Trades Department, AFL, 1939-1947 (Box-folder 2/84)
      - Anderson, Carl, 1942-1953 (Box-folder 2/85)
      - Associated General Contractors, 1937-1965 (Box-folder 2/86)
      - Atkinson, Guy F (Company), 1944-1948 (Box-folder 2/87)
      - Baugh, T. J., 1960 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Better Business Standards Association, Inc, 1952-1956 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Bay Counties District Council of Carpenters (San Francisco), 1937-1949 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Lumber and Sawmill Workers District Council, 1938-1956 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Washington State Council, 1926-1936 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Wash. State Council of Carpenters, 1954-1962 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Carpenters and Joiners Local Union No. 47 (st. Louis, 70), 1948-1950 (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local Union No. 98, 1924-1960 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Sitka Local 466, 1938-1957 (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 756, 1940-1954 (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 770, 1947-1954 (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1174, 1944-1959 (Box-folder 3/12)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1243, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1243, 1947-1960 (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1281 (Anchorage) Part 1, 1938-1951 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1281 (Anchorage) Part 2, 1953-1967 (Box-folder 3/16)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1368 (Renton), 1947-1964 (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1597 (Bremerton), 1939-1942 (Box-folder 3/18)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1708 (Auburn), 1940-1961 (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Strom and Olsen Hardwood Floors, 1939-1982 (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 2162, 1939-1965 (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 2205, 1923-1957 (Box-folder 3/22)
      - Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 2207, 1937-1954 (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Chamber of Commerce, 1933-1962 (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Civilian War Commission, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 3/25)
      - Congress of Industrial Organization, 1940 (Box-folder 3/26)
      - Columbia Valley Authority, 1945 (Box-folder 3/27)
      - Curties Company Clinton, Iowa, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 3/28)
      - Drake Puget Sound Company, 1946-1950 (Box-folder 3/29)
      - Fishing Derby Committee, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 3/30)
      - Fort Flagler, 1955 (Box-folder 3/31)
      - King County Center Blood Bank Inc, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 3/32)
      - International Association of Machinists, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 3/33)
      - Marine and Fishing Industries, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 3/34)
      - Marshall, Frank, 1937-1967 (Box-folder 3/35)
      - Miscellaneous, 1939-1964 (Box-folder 3/36)
      - Ross Dam, 1939-1951 (Box-folder 3/37)
      - Ross Powerhouse Contractors, 1951-1955 (Box-folder 3/38)
      - Seattle Building Trades Council Part 1, 1943-1972 (Box-folder 3/39)
      - Seattle Building Trades Council Part 2, 1936-1943 (Box-folder 3/40)
      - Seattle (city), 1940-1972 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Seattle Police Dept., 1939-1945 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Seattle School Board, 1941-1960 (Box-folder 4/3)
      - Seattle Traffic and Safety Council, 1941-1960 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Special Dispansion to Work Below Wage Scale, 1929-1965 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Stabilization Conference on Alaska Wage Rates, 1938-1949 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Siem Drake Puget Sound Co., 1939-1943 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Timber Structures, Inc, 1943-1948 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Union Register, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - US. Congress, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Washington Benevolent Association, 1939-1942 (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Washington Labor and Industries, 1943-1964 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Washington Legislature, 1941-1954 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Washington Employers, Inc, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Washington New Dealer, 1942 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Subject Series Correspondence, 1955-1967; Subseries D (Box-folder 4/16-4/19)
      - Century 21 Exposition, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Contractors Licensing, 1955-1967 (Box-folder 4/17)
      - Convalescent Hospital Licensing, 1966 (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Unemployment in Alaska, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 4/19)
  - MINUTES, 1922-1967; SERIES IV (Box-folder 4/20-6/6)
    - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289, 1922-1958; Subseries A (Box-folder 4/20-4/24, 4/53-6/6)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289, 1922 (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289, 1924 (Box-folder 4/21)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289, 1923 (Box-folder 4/22)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289, 1930 (Box-folder 4/23)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289, 1931 (Box-folder 4/24)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289, 1932 (Box-folder 4/53)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289, 1940 (Box-folder 4/54)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 1, 1941 (Box-folder 4/55)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 2, 1941 (Box-folder 4/56)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 1, 1942 (Box-folder 4/57)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 2, 1942 (Box-folder 4/58)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 1, 1943 (Box-folder 4/59)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 2, 1943 (Box-folder 4/60)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 1, 1944 (Box-folder 4/61)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 2, 1944 (Box-folder 4/62)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 1, 1945 (Box-folder 4/63)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 2, 1945 (Box-folder 4/64)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289, 1946 (Box-folder 4/65)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 1, 1949 (Box-folder 4/66)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 2, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 4/67)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 1, 1950 (Box-folder 4/68)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Part 2, 1950 (Box-folder 4/69)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289, 1951 (Box-folder 4/70)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes, 1946 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 1, 1945 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 2, 1945 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 3, 1945 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 1, 1944 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 2, 1944 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 3, 1944 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 1, 1943 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 2, 1943 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 3, 1943 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 1, 1942 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 2, 1942 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 3, 1942 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 1, 1941 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 2, 1941 (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 3, 1941 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 1, 1940 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 2, 1940 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 3, 1940 (Box-folder 5/19)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 1, 1939 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 2, 1939 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 3, 1939 (Box-folder 5/22)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 1, 1938 (Box-folder 5/23)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 2, 1938 (Box-folder 5/24)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 3, 1938 (Box-folder 5/25)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes, 1937 (Box-folder 5/26)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes, 1936 (Box-folder 5/27)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes, 1935 (Box-folder 5/28)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes, 1934 (Box-folder 5/29)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes, 1933 (Box-folder 5/30)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes, 1932 (Box-folder 5/31)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 1, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 5/32)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 2, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 5/33)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 3, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 5/34)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 4, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 5/35)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 5, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 5/36)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 6, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 5/37)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 7, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 8, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 9, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 10, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 11, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Carpenters, District Council Local 1289 Financial Statements and Minutes Part 12, 1946-1958 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Joint Apprenticeship Committee, King County, 1939-1967; Subseries B (Box-folder 4/31-4/36)
      - Joint Apprenticeship Committee, King County Part 1, 1939-1948 (Box-folder 4/31)
      - Joint Apprenticeship Committee, King County Part 2, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 4/32)
      - Joint Apprenticeship Committee. King County Part 3, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 4/33)
      - Joint Apprenticeship Committee, King County Part 4, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 4/34)
      - Joint Apprenticeship Committee, King County Part 5, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 4/35)
      - Joint Apprenticeship Committee, King County Part 6, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 4/36)
    - Affiliated Organizations, 1924-1967; Subseries C (Box-folder 4/25-4/31, 4/37-4/52)
      - Alaska Carpenters Negotiating Committee, 1938-1941 (Box-folder 4/25)
      - A.F.L Defense Committee, 1948 (Box-folder 4/26)
      - Board of Trustees of the Carpenter Center, 1955 (Box-folder 4/27)
      - Executive Board, 1931-1933 (Box-folder 4/28)
      - Insulation and Weatherstrip Meeting, 1949 (Box-folder 4/29)
      - Joint Conference Committee, 1930 (Box-folder 4/30)
      - Report of the Secretary, 1932 (Box-folder 4/37)
      - Trial Boards, 1924-1931 (Box-folder 4/38)
      - Carpenter Center, Inc, 1955 (Box-folder 4/39)
      - Local Union's Office Space, 1954 (Box-folder 4/40)
      - Plastic Products Inc. Negotiation, 1959 (Box-folder 4/41)
      - Washington-Northern Idaho District Council and Locals Meeting, 1960 (Box-folder 4/42)
      - Western and Central Washington Area Agreement Caucus, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 4/43)
      - Bay Counties District Council of Carpenters (San Francisco), 1929-1932 (Box-folder 4/44)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Portland District Council, 1924-1937 (Box-folder 4/45)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Tacoma District Council, 1926-1937 (Box-folder 4/46)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Vancouver B.C. District Council, 1929-1932 (Box-folder 4/47)
      - King County Road Funds Committee, 1961 (Box-folder 4/48)
      - Pacific Coast Committee of Marine Carpenters, 1967 (Box-folder 4/49)
      - Pacific Coast Shipbuilding Zone Conference, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 4/50)
      - Seattle Building Trades Council, 1924-1937 (Box-folder 4/51)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Ship Sealers Local 1589, Transportation Committee, 1954 (Box-folder 4/52)
  - AGREEMENTS, 1918-1971; SERIES V (Box-folder 6/7-6/48)
    - Alaska Salmon Industry Part 1, 1940-1959 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Alaska Salmon Industry Part 2, 1937-1954 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Alaska Salmon Industry Part 1, 1942-1953 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Alaska Salmon Industry Part 2, 1954-1960 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Associated General Contractors of America, Mountain Pacific Chapter Part 1, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - Associated General Contractors of America, Mountain Pacific Chapter Part 2, 1941-1947 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - Associated General Contractors of America, Seattle Tacoma Chapters Part 1, 1941-1971 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - Associated General Contractors of America, Seattle Tacoma Chapters Part 2, 1952-1962 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - Associated General Contractors of America, Seattle Tacoma Chapters Part 3, 1947-1962 (Box-folder 6/15)
    - Building Owners and Managers Association, Council of Seattle, 1947 (Box-folder 6/16)
    - Sunset Cabinet Co., 1926 (Box-folder 6/17)
    - Cisco Construction Company Part 1, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6/18)
    - Cisco Construction Company Part 2, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6/19)
    - Columbia Construction Company, 1939 (Box-folder 6/20)
    - Contract No. w-112-eng-1000, 1947 (Box-folder 6/21)
    - Diablo Dam, 1950 (Box-folder 6/22)
    - Drake Puget Sound, Aleutian Islands, 1939-1947 (Box-folder 6/23)
    - Eastside Builders Association, 1956 (Box-folder 6/24)
    - Employers' Association of Washington, Inc., 1936 (Box-folder 6/25)
    - Guy F. Atkinson Company, 1943 (Box-folder 6/26)
    - Iron Workers, 1953-1967 (Box-folder 6/27)
    - King County Board of County Commissioners Part 1, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 6/28)
    - King County Board of County Commissioners Part 2, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 6/29)
    - McNary Dam Project, 1949 (Box-folder 6/30)
    - Millmen Plant Owners of Seattle Wash., 1935-1939 (Box-folder 6/31)
    - Miscellaneous, 1928-1934 (Box-folder 6/32)
    - Mud Mountain Dam, 1939 (Box-folder 6/33)
    - Plastic Products, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 6/34)
    - Ron Rawson, Inc. Part 1, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 6/35)
    - Ron Rawson, Inc. Part 2, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 6/36)
    - Ross Dam Part 1, 1947-1952 (Box-folder 6/37)
    - Ross Dam Part 2, 1939-1952 (Box-folder 6/38)
    - Seattle Construction Council, 1942-1950 (Box-folder 6/39)
    - Seattle Home Builders Association, 1951 (Box-folder 6/40)
    - Seattle Housing Authority, 1947-1966 (Box-folder 6/41)
    - Seattle Master Builders Association, 1918-1941 (Box-folder 6/42)
    - Tacoma Narrows Bridge, 1939 (Box-folder 6/43)
    - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 6/44)
    - US Navy, 1940 (Box-folder 6/45)
    - Strom and Olsen Hardwood Floors, Undated (Box-folder 6/46)
    - Wage Stabilization Board, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 6/47)
    - West Construction Company, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 6/48)
  - TRADE RULES, 1936-1958; SERIES VI (Box-folder 6/49)
    - Trade Rules, 1936-1958 (Box-folder 6/49)
  - WAGE SCALES, 1928-1961; SERIES VII (Box-folder 7/1-7/5)
    - Wage Scales Part 1, 1928-1969 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Wages Scales Part 2, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Wages Scales Part 3, 1944-1970 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Wage Scales Part 4, 1928 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Wage Scales Part 5, 1948-1951 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - PROPOSALS, 1961-1962; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 7/6-7/7)
    - Employers' Proposal, 1961 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Laborers of America-- Central Washington Area Proposal, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 7/7)
  - RESOLUTIONS, 1930-1971; SERIES IX (Box-folder 7/8-7/11)
    - District Council of Carpenters, 1950 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - Lake Washington Bridge, 1953 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Washington State Labor Council Convention, 1971 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1936 (Box-folder 7/11)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS 1924-1964, SERIES X (Box-folder 7/12-7/19)
    - Cisco Construction Company Case, 1954-1957 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Carpenters and Joiners, Seattle District Council Entertainment Committee Part 1, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - Carpenters and Joiners, Seattle District Council Entertainment Committee Part 2, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Carpenters and Joiners, Seattle District Council Entertainment Committee Part 3, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 7/15)
    - Financial Committee, 1924-1933 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - Seattle Convention, 1941-1947 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - U.S. Labor Department Reports, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 7/18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1924-1938 (Box-folder 7/19)
  - REPORTS, 1928-1970; SERIES XI (Box-folder 7/20)
    - Reports, 1928-1970 (Box-folder 7/20)
  - LEGAL DOCUMENTS, 1944-1967; SERIES XII (Box-folder 7/21-7/27)
    - Alaska Salmon Industry Part 1, 1944 (Box-folder 7/21)
    - Alaska Salmon Industry Part 2, 1944 (Box-folder 7/22)
    - Alaska Salmon Industry Part 3, 1944 (Box-folder 7/23)
    - Alaska Salmon Industry Part 4, 1944 (Box-folder 7/24)
    - Alaska Salmon Industry Part 5, 1944 (Box-folder 7/25)
    - Carpenters Local 131 et al v. Cisco Construction Co., 1954-1959 (Box-folder 7/26)
    - District Council of Carpenters v. Ironworkers Local No. 84 et al., 1967 (Box-folder 7/27)
  - LEGISLATION, 1934-1959; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 7/28-7/29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1934-1959 (Box-folder 7/28)
    - Columbia Valley Authority, 1945 (Box-folder 7/29)
  - COURT CASES, 1930-1940; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 7/30-7/32)
    - Lawrence Constantino, et al v. Joseph V. Moreschi, et al, 1940 (Box-folder 7/30)
    - Z. E. Wilder v. O. N. Torgenson, 1934 (Box-folder 7/31)
    - Jay See v. District Council of Carpenters, et al, 1930 -1931 (Box-folder 7/32)
  - CONFERENCES AND CONVENTIONS, 1928-1971; SERIES XV (Box-folder 7/33-7/37)
    - Annual Convention, State, 1934-1938 (Box-folder 7/33)
    - Annual Convention, State, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 7/34)
    - Annual Convention, State, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 7/35)
    - Annual Convention, National, 1928 (Box-folder 7/36)
    - Annual Convention, National, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 7/37)
  - NOTES, 1949-1955; SERIES XVI (Box-folder 7/38)
    - Notes, 1949-1955 (Box-folder 7/38)